Ali Mohamed Sedeek

Profile

ITI graduate, with good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed. Using best practices for web development, including responsive designs, creating websites and interfaces using HTML, CSS, JS and PHP practices, and incorporating data from back-end databases and services. Maintain up-to-date knowledge of industry trends and technologies

Internship

Software Engineering Fundamentals Track, /T/

11/2022 - 03/2023

- Operating Systems and Computer Network Fundamentals
- · Introduction to Programming using C
- Object-Oriented Programming Concepts using C++
- Data Structure, algorithms and Database Fundamentals
- HTML5, CSS3, Responsive and Bootstrap
- JavaScript Fundamentals
- PHP and WordPress

Online Courses

SQL, 365 Data Science

Introduction to python, DataCamp

Introduction to R & Intermediate R, DataCamp

Introduction to Data Analytics, Coursera

Professional Experience

Freelance Recruiter, WorkEgypt

06/2022 - 09/2022

- Conduct screening interviews over the phone.
- Source, screen, schedule, conduct interviews and process all prospective candidates.

Service Planner, NCR Corporation

01/2022 - 05/2022

- Plan, prioritize, assign, and monitor all open work orders for CEs.
- Working with other Service Coordinators to fill any gap or resource shortfall.

Coach Assistant, 6th of October Club

2017 – 2019

- Collaborated with the Sports technical staff to achieve the best results.
- Attended meetings with the board of directors to ensure that the necessary tools are brought to the team.

Education

Misr University for Science and Technology

2016 - 2020

Bachelor Degree in Business Administration, Economics CGPA: 3.91/4 (Ranked 1st on Major)

Languages

English	Arabic
Excellent	Native

Skills

- Working effectively within a team to accomplish key objectives.
- Managing workload, meeting deadlines and being organised at all times.
- Deep understanding of the concepts of programming, strong Background of low level languages like C , C++